

Alisher Musurmonov

Web Developer

I am an interactive and motivated freelance web developer with 2+ years of experience in developing and implementing interactive and user-friendly websites. Strong understanding of cross-browser issues and debugging. Experience with mobile development and responsive design.

- 🔀 alisher.musurmonov89@gmail.com
- O Jizzax, Uzbekistan
- in linkedin.com/in/alisher-musurmonov

- www alisher me
- github.com/Alisher778

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Alitech Website Solutions 🗷

02/2018 - Present

Jizzax, Uzbekistan

Building, designing web application daily basis using modern web development technologies .

Web Developer Vector NJ, LLC

05/2017 - 02/2018

Brooklyn, NY

Built the company website from scratch for better UX and UI.Optimized website performance, SEO and setup database.Collaborated with the designers to create clean and simple interface

PROJECTS

Jizzakh AIDS Center (03/2018 − 06/2018) 🗹

- This was a corporate website development project
- Features: Branding, web design, test app and mobile app
- Built with: Javascript, ¡Query, HTML, ReactJs, Photoshop, Bootstarp
- Website http://jizzax-aids.uz/test

- Fully functional relocation company website
- Features includes user authentication, admin access, responsive design and database implementation
- Built with NodeJs, ExpressJs, Javascript, jQuery, MongoDB, HTML
- Website http://www.prolocalmovers.us/

JS Code Performer (11/2017 - 12/2017) 🗷

- This is a project which provides the performance speed of your javascript code - http://thecodeperformer.com/
- Built with ReactJs, HTML, CSS and Bootstrap 4
- Website http://thecodeperformer.com/

EDUCATION

Web Development

New York Code and Design Academy

09/2015 - 03/2017

New York, NY

Courses

- Full-stack web development
- Back-end web development with Ruby
- Web development 101

Lingustics

Jizzakh State Pedagogical Institute

09/2009 - 06/2013

Jizzakh, Uzbekistan

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Built many websites (08/2014 - Present)

I have been building and developing websites for +3 years

CERTIFICATES

Certificate of Completion (01/2014 - Present)

- Part-Time Web Development Intensive, Web Development 100, Ruby on Rails 101, Computer Science 101, MongoDB, Sass, Git Basics and more

ORGANIZATIONS

Organization Name

LANGUAGES

Uzbek	• • • • •	
English	• • • • •	
Russian	• • 0 0 0	

INTERESTS

